<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Mao&#39;s Homepage</title>
        <link>http://maozhenjiang.com/</link>
        <description>Recent content on Mao&#39;s Homepage</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://maozhenjiang.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>2019 College Student Innovation and Entrepreneurship Training Program Project</title>
        <link>http://maozhenjiang.com/p/research/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://maozhenjiang.com/p/research/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://maozhenjiang.com/p/research/helena-hertz-wWZzXlDpMog-unsplash.jpg" alt="Featured image of post 2019 College Student Innovation and Entrepreneurship Training Program Project" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since the middle of the last century, with the continuous innovation of technology, biological research methods have continued to make progress, such as fluorescence imaging, luminescence imaging, photoacoustic imaging, optical tomography, and a series of blot hybridization methods. A series of advanced technologies combined with computers provide great convenience for modern scientists&#39; data analysis. Due to the continuous improvement of experimental conditions, in order to provide more accurate experimental results, the experimenters have increased the number of samples in the experiment. At the same time, more samples have brought more cumbersome and complex data results analysis. Due to time and cost constraints, biologists will abandon manual statistical methods, and some will go out to seek software companies to obtain better data processing methods. However, there are always some communication gaps between biological researchers and software engineers, so this project attempts to develop a software for processing experimental information from the perspective of biological researchers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because there are complex and diverse branch areas in the biological field itself, this project attempts to study long-term potentiation (LTP) in neurobiology [1] The research direction of the complex biology of experiments such as synaptic plasticity The image is identified and analyzed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Neuroplasticity [2] is the most important characteristic in the animal nervous system. Animals have been cognizant of the outside world from birth, and through the shaping and reshaping of various nerve cells and tissues, such as changes in the proportion of gray matter in the center or changes in the number of synapses, the animal’s nervous system tends to Completeness and development are an important feature of animal growth and development at the individual level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The long-term gain effect [3] is one of several phenomena of synaptic plasticity. Under a certain stimulus (such as chemical stimulation), the activity of the synapse is significantly increased, leading to an increase in the signal transmission details between neurons. The long-term gain effect is mainly used to study human memory, thinking, and nervous system development, and is closely related to diseases such as Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s disease and stroke. In an article reported in 2001, several scientists improved the original method and used the fluorescent dye FM 1-43 (FM1-43 is a bipolar fluorescent dye with hydrophilic groups and lipophilic groups. The clusters are located at the two ends of the molecule. In recent years, it has been used for in vivo labeling of endocytosis and exocytosis membrane-coated particles. In the field of neuroscience, this method can also be used as an important part of labeling functional presynaptic terminals. Tools. [4]), by using tetraethylammonium (TEA) [5] is a common anesthetic drug that blocks potassium ion channels,) or electrical stimulation of a specific frequency (200hz), which can affect the nerves in the hippocampus of the brain The element is stimulated to reflect the strength of the long-term gain effect by measuring the half-life of the brightness change of the vesicle bright spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to the experimental method of Stanislav S. Zakharenko1, Leonard Zablow1 and others [6], the number of vesicles under the two-photon microscope field of view is slightly larger (70-100 per field of view), and the vesicles have mobile behavior. The experiment with this method only needs to set up 3 groups, and each group needs to take a picture with an interval of 10s, and it needs to take at least 400s, so at least 8400 pictures are generated. The Internet has not searched for relevant analysis and statistics software, and has no contact with the original experimental method creators, and the current image processing software cannot meet the analysis needs of the experiment, and manual analysis requires a lot of manpower and time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The focus of this project is to identify the number of vesicles in the picture, as well as the corresponding changes in position and brightness. The difficulty lies in solving the problem of analyzing the movement of vesicles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project is implemented by three people, one of whom has relevant experience in biological laboratories and has a strong interest in biology, and plans to engage in biological-related research in the future. The other two may not be in the Department of Biology, but they have a certain understanding of computer vision. , In the Student Union of Shuli College, I have instructed website construction and program design, understand Java, python and other languages, and can collaborate to complete some projects, which ensures that this project has a certain degree of feasibility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[1]Bliss TV, Collingridge GL (January 1993). &amp;ldquo;A synaptic model of memory: long-term potentiation in the hippocampus&amp;rdquo;. Nature. 361 (6407):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[2] Cooke SF, Bliss TV (July 2006). &amp;ldquo;Plasticity in the human central nervous system&amp;rdquo;. Brain. 129 (Pt 7): 1659–73.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[3]Martin KC, Casadio A, Zhu H, Yaping E, Rose JC, Chen M, Bailey CH, Kandel ER (December 1997). &amp;ldquo;Synapse-specific, long-term facilitation of aplysia sensory to motor synapses: a function for local protein synthesis in memory storage&amp;rdquo;. Cell. 91 (7): 927–38. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[4]https://www.chemdrug.com/article/7/459/2291367.html&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[5]https://baike.baidu.com/item/%E5%9B%9B%E4%B9%99%E8%83%BA/5246636?fr=aladdin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[6]Stanislav S. Zakharenko, Leonard Zablow &amp;amp; Steven A. Siegelbaum  Nature Neurosciencevolume 4, pages711–717 (2001)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;Content&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project mainly uses JAVA language, and may use other languages at the same time. It will initially develop a runnable JAR program or other program, which can basically identify the location, number and brightness changes of the vesicles. Later, under the feedback of the experimenters, after revision Develop a program based on the Android system, and put the program into the Google App Store for sharing if conditions permit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The specific research content is the program development work, and the final assessment results are two, which can basically identify the image and make a simple analysis program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The key problem to be solved is to identify the number, position and brightness changes of vesicles located between neurons after fluorescence staining under a large number of two-photon microscopes, and collect the data, and conduct preliminary analysis through the program based on experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since the proposal of the project is based on actual needs, the project leader has development experience and knowledge accumulation, so it is feasible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;plan&#34;&gt;Plan&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;after investigating the preliminary requirements, the programming ideas were initially determined.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the construction of the framework was realized, which can basically identify and analyze.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;preliminary application planning is carried out to determine the basic functions, required interfaces, and whether database support is required, and build a basic framework.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;complete the interface design, including interface, list, menu buttons, etc., to achieve data operation and storage, and to modify and optimize based on the feedback of the experimenters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;background development and memory optimization, including implementation of garbage&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;collection, adapter optimization and screen adaptation, etc. Carry out the actual test of multiple models of the Android terminal, formulate the user agreement, and release the public beta version on the platform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;when conditions permit, after receiving feedback, the program will be optimized and updated, and the version update and maintenance plan will be finalized, and the official version will be released.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;innovation&#34;&gt;Innovation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project was originally derived from the lack of fast and efficient analysis methods for the large number of images generated in the experimental methods of Stanislav S. Zakharenko1, Leonard Zablow1, etc. Since there are no relevant software analysis tools on the Internet, manual identification will consume a lot of time, energy. As a college student, I currently have the time and energy to make a program to fill the problem of image recognition and data processing in this experimental method. After the software is successfully developed, it can be shared via the Internet, allowing more scholars who use this experimental method to analyze and process experimental results faster and more conveniently.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
        <link>http://maozhenjiang.com/p/markdown-syntax-guide/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://maozhenjiang.com/p/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://maozhenjiang.com/p/markdown-syntax-guide/pawel-czerwinski-8uZPynIu-rQ-unsplash.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Markdown Syntax Guide" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headings&#34;&gt;Headings&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following HTML &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;—&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;h6&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; elements represent six levels of section headings. &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; is the highest section level while &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;h6&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; is the lowest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;h1&#34;&gt;H1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;h2&#34;&gt;H2&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;h3&#34;&gt;H3&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;h4&#34;&gt;H4&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;h5&#34;&gt;H5&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;h6&#34;&gt;H6&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;paragraph&#34;&gt;Paragraph&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Xerum, quo qui aut unt expliquam qui dolut labo. Aque venitatiusda cum, voluptionse latur sitiae dolessi aut parist aut dollo enim qui voluptate ma dolestendit peritin re plis aut quas inctum laceat est volestemque commosa as cus endigna tectur, offic to cor sequas etum rerum idem sintibus eiur? Quianimin porecus evelectur, cum que nis nust voloribus ratem aut omnimi, sitatur? Quiatem. Nam, omnis sum am facea corem alique molestrunt et eos evelece arcillit ut aut eos eos nus, sin conecerem erum fuga. Ri oditatquam, ad quibus unda veliamenimin cusam et facea ipsamus es exerum sitate dolores editium rerore eost, temped molorro ratiae volorro te reribus dolorer sperchicium faceata tiustia prat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Itatur? Quiatae cullecum rem ent aut odis in re eossequodi nonsequ idebis ne sapicia is sinveli squiatum, core et que aut hariosam ex eat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;blockquotes&#34;&gt;Blockquotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The blockquote element represents content that is quoted from another source, optionally with a citation which must be within a &lt;code&gt;footer&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;cite&lt;/code&gt; element, and optionally with in-line changes such as annotations and abbreviations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;blockquote-without-attribution&#34;&gt;Blockquote without attribution&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tiam, ad mint andaepu dandae nostion secatur sequo quae.
&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt; that you can use &lt;em&gt;Markdown syntax&lt;/em&gt; within a blockquote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;blockquote-with-attribution&#34;&gt;Blockquote with attribution&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t communicate by sharing memory, share memory by communicating.&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
— &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Rob Pike&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;tables&#34;&gt;Tables&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tables aren&amp;rsquo;t part of the core Markdown spec, but Hugo supports supports them out-of-the-box.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Name&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Age&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Bob&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;27&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Alice&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;23&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;inline-markdown-within-tables&#34;&gt;Inline Markdown within tables&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Italics&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Bold&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Code&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;em&gt;italics&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;code&gt;code&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;code-blocks&#34;&gt;Code Blocks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;code-block-with-backticks&#34;&gt;Code block with backticks&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-html&#34; data-lang=&#34;html&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cp&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;!doctype html&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;html&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;lang&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;en&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;head&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;meta&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;charset&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;utf-8&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;title&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;Example HTML5 Document&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;title&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;head&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;body&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;p&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;Test&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;p&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;body&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;html&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h4 id=&#34;code-block-indented-with-four-spaces&#34;&gt;Code block indented with four spaces&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;!doctype html&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;html lang=&amp;quot;en&amp;quot;&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;head&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;meta charset=&amp;quot;utf-8&amp;quot;&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;title&amp;gt;Example HTML5 Document&amp;lt;/title&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/head&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;body&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Test&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/body&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/html&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;code-block-with-hugos-internal-highlight-shortcode&#34;&gt;Code block with Hugo&amp;rsquo;s internal highlight shortcode&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-html&#34; data-lang=&#34;html&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cp&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;!doctype html&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;html&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;lang&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;en&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;head&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;meta&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;charset&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;utf-8&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;title&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;Example HTML5 Document&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;title&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;head&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;body&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;p&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;Test&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;p&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;body&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;html&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;list-types&#34;&gt;List Types&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;ordered-list&#34;&gt;Ordered List&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First item&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Second item&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Third item&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;unordered-list&#34;&gt;Unordered List&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;List item&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Another item&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And another item&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;nested-list&#34;&gt;Nested list&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fruit
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Orange&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Banana&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dairy
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Milk&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cheese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;other-elements--abbr-sub-sup-kbd-mark&#34;&gt;Other Elements — abbr, sub, sup, kbd, mark&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;GIF&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; is a bitmap image format.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;H&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;2&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;O&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;X&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;n&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; + Y&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;n&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; = Z&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;n&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Press &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;CTRL&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;+&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;ALT&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;+&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Delete&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; to end the session.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;salamanders&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; are nocturnal, and hunt for insects, worms, and other small creatures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;section class=&#34;footnotes&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnotes&#34;&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:1&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The above quote is excerpted from Rob Pike&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PAAkCSZUG1c&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;talk&lt;/a&gt; during Gopherfest, November 18, 2015. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Placeholder Text</title>
        <link>http://maozhenjiang.com/p/placeholder-text/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://maozhenjiang.com/p/placeholder-text/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://maozhenjiang.com/p/placeholder-text/matt-le-SJSpo9hQf7s-unsplash.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Placeholder Text" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de pectora summo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Redit teque digerit hominumque toris verebor lumina non cervice subde tollit usus habet Arctonque, furores quas nec ferunt. Quoque montibus nunc caluere tempus inhospita parcite confusaque translucet patri vestro qui optatis lumine cognoscere flos nubis! Fronde ipsamque patulos Dryopen deorum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exierant elisi ambit vivere dedere&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Duce pollice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eris modo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spargitque ferrea quos palude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rursus nulli murmur; hastile inridet ut ab gravi sententia! Nomine potitus silentia flumen, sustinet placuit petis in dilapsa erat sunt. Atria tractus malis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comas hunc haec pietate fetum procerum dixit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post torum vates letum Tiresia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flumen querellas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Arcanaque montibus omnes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quidem et&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;vagus-elidunt&#34;&gt;Vagus elidunt&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Canons_of_page_construction#Van_de_Graaf_canon&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;The Van de Graaf Canon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;mane-refeci-capiebant-unda-mulcebat&#34;&gt;Mane refeci capiebant unda mulcebat&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Victa caducifer, malo vulnere contra dicere aurato, ludit regale, voca! Retorsit colit est profanae esse virescere furit nec; iaculi matertera et visa est, viribus. Divesque creatis, tecta novat collumque vulnus est, parvas. &lt;strong&gt;Faces illo pepulere&lt;/strong&gt; tempus adest. Tendit flamma, ab opes virum sustinet, sidus sequendo urbis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Iubar proles corpore raptos vero auctor imperium; sed et huic: manus caeli Lelegas tu lux. Verbis obstitit intus oblectamina fixis linguisque ausus sperare Echionides cornuaque tenent clausit possit. Omnia putatur. Praeteritae refert ausus; ferebant e primus lora nutat, vici quae mea ipse. Et iter nil spectatae vulnus haerentia iuste et exercebat, sui et.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eurytus Hector, materna ipsumque ut Politen, nec, nate, ignari, vernum cohaesit sequitur. Vel &lt;strong&gt;mitis temploque&lt;/strong&gt; vocatus, inque alis, &lt;em&gt;oculos nomen&lt;/em&gt; non silvis corpore coniunx ne displicet illa. Crescunt non unus, vidit visa quantum inmiti flumina mortis facto sic: undique a alios vincula sunt iactata abdita! Suspenderat ego fuit tendit: luna, ante urbem Propoetides &lt;strong&gt;parte&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Math Typesetting</title>
        <link>http://maozhenjiang.com/p/math-typesetting/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://maozhenjiang.com/p/math-typesetting/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Mathematical notation in a Hugo project can be enabled by using third party JavaScript libraries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this example we will be using &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://katex.org/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;KaTeX&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create a partial under &lt;code&gt;/layouts/partials/math.html&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Within this partial reference the &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://katex.org/docs/autorender.html&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Auto-render Extension&lt;/a&gt; or host these scripts locally.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include the partial in your templates like so:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34; data-lang=&#34;bash&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;{{&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;if&lt;/span&gt; or .Params.math .Site.Params.math &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;}}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;{{&lt;/span&gt; partial &lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;math.html&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt; . &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;}}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;{{&lt;/span&gt; end &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;}}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To enable KaTex globally set the parameter &lt;code&gt;math&lt;/code&gt; to &lt;code&gt;true&lt;/code&gt; in a project&amp;rsquo;s configuration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To enable KaTex on a per page basis include the parameter &lt;code&gt;math: true&lt;/code&gt; in content files&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; Use the online reference of &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://katex.org/docs/supported.html&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Supported TeX Functions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;examples&#34;&gt;Examples&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Block math:
$$
\varphi = 1+\frac{1} {1+\frac{1} {1+\frac{1} {1+\cdots} } } 
$$&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Emoji Support</title>
        <link>http://maozhenjiang.com/p/emoji-support/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://maozhenjiang.com/p/emoji-support/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://maozhenjiang.com/p/emoji-support/the-creative-exchange-d2zvqp3fpro-unsplash.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Emoji Support" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/functions/emojify/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;&lt;code&gt;emojify&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; function can be called directly in templates or &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/templates/shortcode-templates/#inline-shortcodes&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Inline Shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To enable emoji globally, set &lt;code&gt;enableEmoji&lt;/code&gt; to &lt;code&gt;true&lt;/code&gt; in your site&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/getting-started/configuration/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;configuration&lt;/a&gt; and then you can type emoji shorthand codes directly in content files; e.g.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;http://www.emoji-cheat-sheet.com/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Emoji cheat sheet&lt;/a&gt; is a useful reference for emoji shorthand codes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;N.B.&lt;/strong&gt; The above steps enable Unicode Standard emoji characters and sequences in Hugo, however the rendering of these glyphs depends on the browser and the platform. To style the emoji you can either use a third party emoji font or a font stack; e.g.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-html&#34; data-lang=&#34;html&#34;&gt;.emoji {
  font-family: Apple Color Emoji, Segoe UI Emoji, NotoColorEmoji, Segoe UI Symbol, Android Emoji, EmojiSymbols;
}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
